DANIELLE RAGAS

danielleragas.me ragasdanielle@gmail.com +1 604 353 7945

SKILLS

Storyboarding Graphic Design Motion Graphics Video Editing Illustration Sketching Writing

TOOLS

Adobe Creative Suite Autodesk Maya HTML/CSS Unity 3D Final Cut Pro

INTERESTS

Gaming

I love RPGs and nonlinear gameplay. Currently playing Prey and Overwatch.

Illustration

I've created original and fan work under the artist name Tsuyuus since 2014.

EDUCATION

Technology

Simon Fraser University

BA in Interactive Arts and

2013 - present

ABOUT

I'm an artist and designer from Vancouver with a passion for illustration, animation, video editing, and storytelling. I strive to create memorable experiences, and I can bring my creativity and strong communication skills to any project and position.

EXPERIENCE

ASSOCIATE ARTIST / BIOWARE

sept 2017 - aug 2018

Produced ten storyboards for cinematic cutscenes and gameplay moments for two different projects.

Routinely presented boards to writers, animators, and designers to identify problems with scenes, come up with appropriate solutions, and iterate on feedback.

DESIGNER AND ARTIST / BEEP

jan 2017 - apr 2017 / academic project, video game

Created environment concept art, game mechanic diagrams, and game assets for a 3D action adventure puzzle game.

Designed and built four of nine levels in the Unity game engine.

ANIMATOR AND EDITOR / AMORPHOUS

jan 2016 - apr 2016 / academic project, short film

Modeled and animated the main character and two environments for a 3 minute long 3D animated film about an astronaut on an alien planet.

Compiled rendered shots together and added visual effects such as backgrounds and holographic screens.

MARKETING ASSISTANT / APPLIED BIOLOGICAL MATERIALS

sept 2016 - dec 2016

Designed various website assets and print material for both public and in-house use according to the company's existing style guide.

Recorded audio for and animated two 8 minute videos illustrating biotechnology concepts for the company's YouTube channel.